[
  {
  "optionA": "suffer",
  "optionB": "suffers",
  "optionC": "suffering",
  "optionD": "suffered",
  "answer": "suffered",
  "question": "The assets of Marble Faun Publishing Company ___ last quarter when one of their main local distributors went out of business."
},
  {
  "optionA": "him",
  "optionB": "his",
  "optionC": "himself",
  "optionD": "he",
  "answer": "his",
  "question": "lndie film director Luke Steele will be in London for the premiere of ___ new movie."
},
  {
  "optionA": "full",
  "optionB": "complete",
  "optionC": "all",
  "optionD": "total",
  "answer": "all",
  "question": "Laboratory employees are expected to wear a name tag and carry identification at ___ times."
},
  {
  "optionA": "method",
  "optionB": "guide",
  "optionC": "staff",
  "optionD": "role",
  "answer": "guide",
  "question": "The latest training ___ contains tips on teaching a second language to international students:"
},
  {
  "optionA": "qualified",
  "optionB": "qualifications",
  "optionC": "qualify",
  "optionD": "qualifying",
  "answer": "qualifications",
  "question": "Once you have your resume with references and ___ , please submit it to the Human Resources Department on the 3rd floor."
},
 {
  "optionA": "soon",
  "optionB": "shortly",
  "optionC": "recently",
  "optionD": "yet",
  "answer": "recently",
  "question": "Ursa Major Corp. has ___ negotiated a deal with a Russian competitor in surveying the Kamchatka Peninsula."
},
  {
  "optionA": "having",
  "optionB": "will have",
  "optionC": "was having",
  "optionD": "has",
  "answer": "was having",
  "question": "Ms. Cho relayed her concerns about the company's financial situation while she ___ a meeting with the manager."
},
  {
  "optionA": "necessary",
  "optionB": "necessarily",
  "optionC": "necessitate",
  "optionD": "necessity",
  "answer": "necessary",
  "question": "Whether it is ___ to register for a student discount card depends on the needs of the individual."
},
  {
  "optionA": "materials",
  "optionB": "sessions",
  "optionC": "experiences",
  "optionD": "positions",
  "answer": "sessions",
  "question": "Even experienced clerks are encouraged to attend training ___ to keep them updated on new ideas in the world of banking."
},
  {
  "optionA": "they",
  "optionB": "them",
  "optionC": "their",
  "optionD": "themselves",
  "answer": "themselves",
  "question": "Workers are advised not to operate certain machines by ___ ."
},
  {
  "optionA": "construct",
  "optionB": "constructive",
  "optionC": "construction",
  "optionD": "constructed",
  "answer": "construction",
  "question": ". The ___ of a discount department store was delayed by the protests of several members of the community."
},
  {
  "optionA": "large",
  "optionB": "largely",
  "optionC": "largest",
  "optionD": "larger",
  "answer": "largely",
  "question": "Ms. Maria Perreira is ___ responsible for some of our company's most successful marketing campaigns."
},
  {
  "optionA": "estimates",
  "optionB": "sponsors",
  "optionC": "deliverance",
  "optionD": "relocations",
  "answer": "estimates",
  "question": "Mr. Singh requested ___ from several catering companies before making his decision."
},
  {
  "optionA": "despite",
  "optionB": "due to",
  "optionC": "provided that",
  "optionD": "because",
  "answer": "due to",
  "question": "Our apartment building's occupancy increased ___ the efforts of our knowledgeable and friendly rental agent, Ms. Gova."
},
  {
  "optionA": "among",
  "optionB": "since",
  "optionC": "within",
  "optionD": "whereas",
  "answer": "within",
  "question": "Those employees wishing to change departments ___ the company may send their inquiries to Mr. Alvarez."
},
  {
  "optionA": "procedure",
  "optionB": "layer",
  "optionC": "accessory",
  "optionD": "quality",
  "answer": "quality",
  "question": "The New Economic Quarterly criticized the ___ of all new products produced by Yun Sung Industrial Co., Ltd."
},
  {
  "optionA": "led",
  "optionB": "leads",
  "optionC": "leader",
  "optionD": "leading",
  "answer": "leading",
  "question": "One of the ___ international research facilities in botany is located at the Hoskin Museum of Natural History."
},
  {
  "optionA": "instituted",
  "optionB": "proved",
  "optionC": "decided",
  "optionD": "resembled",
  "answer": "instituted",
  "question": "In order to ensure customer safety, the government has ___ a new set of guidelines for pharmaceutical companies."
},
  {
  "optionA": "allowing",
  "optionB": "allows",
  "optionC": "allowance",
  "optionD": "allowably",
  "answer": "allowing",
  "question": "Welton Textiles Inc. made a net profit of $ million, ___ it to fund its expansion across the continent."
},
  {
  "optionA": "comparative",
  "optionB": "envious",
  "optionC": "pleased",
  "optionD": "ambitious",
  "answer": "ambitious",
  "question": "Our ___ production goals will be directed by a skilled team of qualified managers."
},
{
        "optionA": "increasingly",
        "optionB": "increasing",
        "optionC": "increased",
        "optionD": "increase",
        "answer": "increasingly",
        "question": "Prattchet Co. has ___ turned to making most of its products from recycled materials."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "Bringing",
        "optionB": "Helping",
        "optionC": "Maintaining",
        "optionD": "Promoting",
        "answer": "Maintaining",
        "question": "___ our financial goals for this year may require cutting back on some overhead costs."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "of",
        "optionB": "for",
        "optionC": "with",
        "optionD": "to",
        "answer": "with",
        "question": "Heidelberg Publishing Co. offers employees ___ performance bonuses to encourage success."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "gradually",
        "optionB": "nearly",
        "optionC": "exclusively",
        "optionD": "precisely",
        "answer": "exclusively",
        "question": "An anniversary dinner was held ___ for high-ranking officials in the corporation."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "During",
        "optionB": "Until",
        "optionC": "After",
        "optionD": "When",
        "answer": "When",
        "question": "___ contacting our Human Resources Department by phone, please include your contact information."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "satisfied",
        "optionB": "spacious",
        "optionC": "considerable",
        "optionD": "capable",
        "answer": "spacious",
        "question": "Because of the added guests from our allied financial firm, a more ___ meeting room had to be used than usual."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "energy",
        "optionB": "energize",
        "optionC": "energetic",
        "optionD": "energetically",
        "answer": "energetic",
        "question": "Ms. Richards has been an exceptionally ___ member of the marketing team, providing Billingsgate Enterprises with great service for nine years."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "Subsequently",
        "optionB": "However",
        "optionC": "Meanwhile",
        "optionD": "Despite",
        "answer": "Despite",
        "question": "___ his falling out with his former employer, Mr. Lee still meets with some of his old co-workers from time to time."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "appreciation",
        "optionB": "appreciative",
        "optionC": "appreciating",
        "optionD": "appreciates",
        "answer": "appreciation",
        "question": "The chief financial officer of Waterhouse Inc. is expressing ___ concerning his predecessor's informative advice."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "competed",
        "optionB": "became",
        "optionC": "continued",
        "optionD": "thought",
        "answer": "became",
        "question": "Since opening last year, Savannah Safari Park quickly ___ one of the leading recreational spots in the region."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "will",
        "optionB": "is",
        "optionC": "was",
        "optionD": "has been",
        "answer": "was",
        "question": ". Ms. Gamble, who ___ an influential literary critic in the s, is now a contributing writer to the National Gazette newspaper."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "arbitrarily",
        "optionB": "separately",
        "optionC": "definitely",
        "optionD": "mutually",
        "answer": "separately",
        "question": "Remember to list fixed expenses ___ from variable expenses."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "probable",
        "optionB": "probability",
        "optionC": "probably",
        "optionD": "probabilities",
        "answer": "probable",
        "question": "The loss of our foreign manufacturing plants may be a ___ outcome of the new plans being implemented."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "environments",
        "optionB": "environmentalists",
        "optionC": "environmentally",
        "optionD": "environmental",
        "answer": "environmentally",
        "question": "New government regulations concerning the chemicals in cleaning solutions mean that the solvents must be as ___ safe as possible."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "consult",
        "optionB": "make",
        "optionC": "invite",
        "optionD": "request",
        "answer": "consult",
        "question": "Ms. Stanhope always tries to ___ her colleagues on the budget."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "originator",
        "optionB": "original",
        "optionC": "originally",
        "optionD": "originality",
        "answer": "original",
        "question": "Rosalind Media Ltd. came up with the idea to hire artists to create ___ artworks for the purpose of marketing."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "approximate",
        "optionB": "important",
        "optionC": "uncertain",
        "optionD": "intended",
        "answer": "uncertain",
        "question": "The CEO of Lawrence United Co. is still ___ about opening company branches in Mexico."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "intention",
        "optionB": "intended",
        "optionC": "intentional",
        "optionD": "intending",
        "answer": "intention",
        "question": "The ___ of Mr. Alex Hartham was to initiate a merger with Culford International."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "throughout",
        "optionB": "against",
        "optionC": "next",
        "optionD": "near",
        "answer": "near",
        "question": "The staff lounge is ___ the meeting room, across the hall from the computer lab."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "implemented",
        "optionB": "induced",
        "optionC": "surprised",
        "optionD": "granted",
        "answer": "granted",
        "question": "The manager ___ Mr. Karnes a promotion because of his successful handling of the company's accounting for the past two years."
    },
	{
        "optionA": "ceremony",
        "optionB": "advice",
        "optionC": "product",
        "optionD": "invention",
        "answer": "ceremony",
        "question": "The awards ___ will begin at approximately 6:00 this evening, at which time winners are requested to be present to receive their awards."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "replace",
        "optionB": "cause",
        "optionC": "interfere",
        "optionD": "return",
        "answer": "replace",
        "question": "For defective merchandise, we will gladly ___ the product or give you a full refund."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "contract",
        "optionB": "contracts",
        "optionC": "contracted",
        "optionD": "contracting",
        "answer": "contract",
        "question": "At the same time, the company also won a two-million-dollar ___ for maintenance of the trains for the next seven years."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "revising",
        "optionB": "revision",
        "optionC": "revise",
        "optionD": "revised",
        "answer": "revised",
        "question": "We are planning to implement a ___ paper-recycling program for all branch offices effective next month."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "ours",
        "optionB": "these",
        "optionC": "us",
        "optionD": "his",
        "answer": "his",
        "question": "Mr. Ken O'Hara, Chief Executive of ESB, after more than 40 years service with the company, has announced ___ decision to retire in July ."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "subjected",
        "optionB": "restored",
        "optionC": "recommended",
        "optionD": "opened",
        "answer": "recommended",
        "question": "Dieting during pregnancy is never ___ , as it can limit the nutrition available to the baby."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "enormously",
        "optionB": "financially",
        "optionC": "exceptionally",
        "optionD": "generously",
        "answer": "generously",
        "question": "Open Society Institute has ___ offered to sponsor a number of participants from developing countries for attendance at the OA Workshop."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "along",
        "optionB": "during",
        "optionC": "of",
        "optionD": "into",
        "answer": "of",
        "question": "If you would like a demonstration ___ the new product, just ask the BKM staff at the booth."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "discussion",
        "optionB": "goal",
        "optionC": "group",
        "optionD": "happening",
        "answer": "discussion",
        "question": "The sales manager has been asked to lead a ___ of the Asian market's future outlook during the board meeting tonight at 7 p.m."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "subsequent",
        "optionB": "subsequent to",
        "optionC": "subsequently",
        "optionD": "subsequence",
        "answer": "subsequently",
        "question": "NDRC is the national authority that is in charge of setting guidance tariffs that are ___ implemented by the local authorities."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "While",
        "optionB": "Yet",
        "optionC": "Rather",
        "optionD": "As though",
        "answer": "While",
        "question": "___ the CEO was giving a speech to the newly hired employees at the training session, a secretary took a picture of him."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "will begin",
        "optionB": "had begun",
        "optionC": "has begun",
        "optionD": "is beginning",
        "answer": "had begun",
        "question": "The company ___ working on the project for the main office even before it chose the land to build on."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "plain",
        "optionB": "public",
        "optionC": "subject",
        "optionD": "general",
        "answer": "subject",
        "question": "Reservations are made on a first-come, first-served basis and are ___ to room availability."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "sharp",
        "optionB": "sharply",
        "optionC": "sharpen",
        "optionD": "sharpness",
        "answer": "sharply",
        "question": "We expect our sales to rise ___ to around $ million over the next 24 months."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "hers",
        "optionB": "herself",
        "optionC": "her own",
        "optionD": "she",
        "answer": "her own",
        "question": "Ruth Akorful is a baker and has been managing ___ business for several years."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "depend",
        "optionB": "dependable",
        "optionC": "dependent",
        "optionD": "dependence",
        "answer": "dependent",
        "question": "The Leighton Group is a service-based organization and our success is ___ on the quality of the service we offer."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "specialty",
        "optionB": "composition",
        "optionC": "priorities",
        "optionD": "negotiations",
        "answer": "negotiations",
        "question": "After months of ___ , we are pleased to announce that the company and your union have reached an agreement that resolves 9 out of 1Opending grievances."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "acquainted",
        "optionB": "acquainting",
        "optionC": "acquaintance",
        "optionD": "acquaintances",
        "answer": "acquaintances",
        "question": "Michael, the former CEO of the company, is looking forward to seeing many friends and ___ at next year's show in August."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "fluently",
        "optionB": "currently",
        "optionC": "considerably",
        "optionD": "originally",
        "answer": "originally",
        "question": "The building built by Emaar Properties was ___ scheduled to be completed at the end of this year but the target date has been changed due to revisions in the building's design."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "will create",
        "optionB": "was created",
        "optionC": "having created",
        "optionD": "had been creating",
        "answer": "will create",
        "question": "Following the visit to your production facility in Hong Kong next week, we ___ a comprehensive factory automation program to meet your company's needs."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "among",
        "optionB": "up",
        "optionC": "at",
        "optionD": "of",
        "answer": "at",
        "question": "Either the marketing director or the sales manager will represent Centum Construction Inc. ___ the Bexco Architecture Conference."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "instruct",
        "optionB": "instructing",
        "optionC": "instructions",
        "optionD": "instructional",
        "answer": "instructions",
        "question": "Your new coffee machine comes with detailed ___ which will help you use it more effectively."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "When",
        "optionB": "Before",
        "optionC": "Whereas",
        "optionD": "Since",
        "answer": "Since",
        "question": "___ she joined our company three years ago, Mrs. Mashimo has greatly expanded our customer base."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "universe",
        "optionB": "universal",
        "optionC": "universally",
        "optionD": "universality",
        "answer": "universally",
        "question": "Neobucks has more than 3, stores in the United States and 25 other countries, and its logo is ___ recognizable."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "complete",
        "optionB": "completion",
        "optionC": "completed",
        "optionD": "completely",
        "answer": "complete",
        "question": "If you would like to comment on a recent experience with us, please ___ a customer satisfaction survey before leaving your room."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "approve",
        "optionB": "express",
        "optionC": "register",
        "optionD": "record",
        "answer": "register",
        "question": "As space is limited, be sure to contact Bill in the personnel department a minimum of three days in advance to ___ for a workshop."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "environment",
        "optionB": "participation",
        "optionC": "reaction",
        "optionD": "incident",
        "answer": "environment",
        "question": "As a manager, you are also responsible for maintaining a work ___ that is comfortable and ergonomically safe."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "heavy",
        "optionB": "forceful",
        "optionC": "steep",
        "optionD": "strict",
        "answer": "steep",
        "question": "The tree-lined trails and ___ slopes make Whistler Mountain a dangerous place to ride, even for experienced cyclists."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "any of",
        "optionB": "each",
        "optionC": "all",
        "optionD": "every",
        "answer": "all",
        "question": "Many people prefer to shop at The Bay Department Store as it offers a lifetime warranty on ___ purchases."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "act",
        "optionB": "progress",
        "optionC": "chance",
        "optionD": "number",
        "answer": "act",
        "question": "In an unprecedented ___ of generosity, Patty DeDominic, the founder of DeDominic & Associates, pledged a $1-million donation that will help local charities."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "calendar",
        "optionB": "intention",
        "optionC": "deadline",
        "optionD": "admission",
        "answer": "deadline",
        "question": "Satyam Computer Services Ltd. has extended the ___ for submitting applications for the marketing manager position to April 13th."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "later",
        "optionB": "recent",
        "optionC": "further",
        "optionD": "following",
        "answer": "later",
        "question": "If mechanical problems occur at the time of your scheduled trip, alternatives will be discussed with you whether to reschedule the trip for a ___ time."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "estimate",
        "optionB": "estimates",
        "optionC": "estimated",
        "optionD": "estimating",
        "answer": "estimate",
        "question": "All work will be discussed in detail before a written ___ is given to any client."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "recalled",
        "optionB": "collaborated",
        "optionC": "provided",
        "optionD": "employed",
        "answer": "collaborated",
        "question": "We have ___ with community groups and business partners to support local economic development projects."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "approached",
        "optionB": "detailed",
        "optionC": "probable",
        "optionD": "loyal",
        "answer": "detailed",
        "question": "All sales representatives should know ___ information about the product they are selling and be able to answer any questions."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "making",
        "optionB": "make",
        "optionC": "makes",
        "optionD": "made",
        "answer": "make",
        "question": "Mountain Equipment Co-op. has deeply discounted their winter items to ___ room for the new spring merchandise."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "in",
        "optionB": "through",
        "optionC": "with",
        "optionD": "along",
        "answer": "in",
        "question": "While ___ a foreign country, it would be wise to take only what you will absolutely need during the day and leave anything else in the safe in your hotel room."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "those",
        "optionB": "them",
        "optionC": "whose",
        "optionD": "which",
        "answer": "those",
        "question": "At the annual stockholders' meeting, large printed material will be made available on request for ___ with visual impairment."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "what",
        "optionB": "that",
        "optionC": "which",
        "optionD": "those",
        "answer": "that",
        "question": "A recent survey indicates ___ young women in particular are showing a strong preference for online shopping."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "responsibility",
        "optionB": "responsibilities",
        "optionC": "responsible",
        "optionD": "responsibly",
        "answer": "responsible",
        "question": "The office manager is ___ for supporting staff members and ensuring that their work is done efficiently."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "her",
        "optionB": "hers",
        "optionC": "herself",
        "optionD": "she",
        "answer": "she",
        "question": "After Rachel had worked for the company for more than 10 years, ___ was finally promoted to a managerial position."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "between",
        "optionB": "both",
        "optionC": "either",
        "optionD": "rather",
        "answer": "both",
        "question": "Mr. Jackson expressed a strong desire to increase ___ the company's revenue and the number of employees."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "produce",
        "optionB": "produces",
        "optionC": "product",
        "optionD": "producing",
        "answer": "produces",
        "question": "Kelvin Video System's most recent model ___ vivid images on its screen."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "From",
        "optionB": "Of",
        "optionC": "For",
        "optionD": "By",
        "answer": "For",
        "question": "___ further information, please don't hesitate to call our customer service center at 1-."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "Enter",
        "optionB": "Entries",
        "optionC": "Being entered",
        "optionD": "Entering",
        "answer": "Entries",
        "question": "___ for the annual GRR contest should be submitted by no later than December 1st."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "easily",
        "optionB": "easy",
        "optionC": "easing",
        "optionD": "ease",
        "answer": "easily",
        "question": "Clients of Bank of America can ___ gain access to their accounts 24 hours a day throughout the year."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "excellent",
        "optionB": "interested",
        "optionC": "grateful",
        "optionD": "absolute",
        "answer": "excellent",
        "question": "The president of the company gave credit for the increased number of sales to the ___ work done by his staff."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "where",
        "optionB": "when",
        "optionC": "there",
        "optionD": "why",
        "answer": "there",
        "question": "Although the owner of the company wasn't able to attend the meeting, his secretary was ___ to take important notes for him."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "even though",
        "optionB": "because of",
        "optionC": "since",
        "optionD": "besides",
        "answer": "because of",
        "question": "The Wall Street banks collapsed ___ the uncertainty that investors had about the American economy."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "begin",
        "optionB": "hurry",
        "optionC": "prevent",
        "optionD": "enhance",
        "answer": "prevent",
        "question": "Wiping out the company's data on retiring workers' computers may ___ any leak concerning crucial information aboutthe company."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "once",
        "optionB": "far",
        "optionC": "yet",
        "optionD": "still",
        "answer": "still",
        "question": "After a long speech about the importance of working hard, Mr. Glenn ___ reminded his workers to work hard every day."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "arranges",
        "optionB": "arranged",
        "optionC": "arranging",
        "optionD": "arrangements",
        "answer": "arrangements",
        "question": "EMI requires all of its employees to make their own ___ for their business trips."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "numerical",
        "optionB": "numbers",
        "optionC": "number",
        "optionD": "numerous",
        "answer": "number",
        "question": "The ___ of flood victims temporarily residing in the government-supplied camps has just exceeded a thousand."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "license",
        "optionB": "licensor",
        "optionC": "licensing",
        "optionD": "licensed",
        "answer": "license",
        "question": "Before obtaining a ___ , applicants are required to complete 40 hours of driving with an adult over 21."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "slowly",
        "optionB": "nearly",
        "optionC": "primarily",
        "optionD": "variously",
        "answer": "primarily",
        "question": "My application was to be reviewed ___ because I attended the company's summer internship course."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "them",
        "optionB": "their",
        "optionC": "those",
        "optionD": "they",
        "answer": "they",
        "question": "All the temporary workers are supposed to keep track of the hours that ___ work."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "quickly",
        "optionB": "quicken",
        "optionC": "quickened",
        "optionD": "quickness",
        "answer": "quickly",
        "question": "Ms. Hong was forced to resign as CEO of the company ___ since investors weren't pleased with her recent performance."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "at",
        "optionB": "with",
        "optionC": "on",
        "optionD": "over",
        "answer": "on",
        "question": "All the employees at SEI Corporation are invited to the meeting ___ the new internal communications system that the company is about to bring in."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "is editing",
        "optionB": "was editing",
        "optionC": "will be editing",
        "optionD": "has been edited",
        "answer": "has been edited",
        "question": "Although the marketing department submitted the initial proposal, it ___ many times since then."
    },
    {
        "optionA": "unwilling",
        "optionB": "unfavorable",
        "optionC": "opposing",
        "optionD": "reluctant",
        "answer": "unfavorable",
        "question": "The president has just realized that the launch of our new product must be postponed owing to ___ conditions in the market."
    }


]